------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
USER
------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

// get current (logged) user as UserDto
GET: localhost:8008/api/user/hello

GET: localhost:8008/api/user/all

GET: localhost:8008/api/user?index=1

POST: localhost:8008/api/user
{
    "name": "ania",
    "password": "123456"
}

------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
SET OF FLASHCARDS
------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

GET: localhost:8008/api/set/all

GET: localhost:8008/api/set?index=1

//post both new set of flashcards and all new flashcards:
POST: localhost:8008/api/admin/set
{
    "category": "IT",
    "name": "git commands",
    "flashcards": [
                    {
                        "question": "git init",
                        "answer": "Create a new local repository"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "git clone /path/to/repository",
                        "answer": "Create a working copy of a local repository"
                    },
                    {
                         "question": "git pull",
                         "answer": "Fetch and merge changes on the remote server to your working directory"
                    }
    ]
}

------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
FLASHCARD
------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

GET: localhost:8008/api/flashcard/all

GET: localhost:8008/api/flashcard?index=1

------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
GAME
------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

GET: localhost:8008/api/game/all

GET: localhost:8008/api/game?index=1

//get games for current user
GET: localhost:8008/api/game/user/current

//get games by user id
GET: localhost:8008/api/game/user?index=1

DELETE: localhost:8008/api/admin/game
    {
        "id": 1,
        "date": "2021-06-13T13:45:21.827245",
        "points": 0,
        "gameMode": "flashcards",
        "ranking": false,
        "setOfFlashcards": {
            "id": 1,
            "category": "IT",
            "name": "linux commands",
            "flashcards": [
                {
                    "id": 1,
                    "question": "bourne-again shell",
                    "answer": "bash"
                },
                {
                    "id": 3,
                    "question": "concatenate and print",
                    "answer": "cat"
                },
                {
                    "id": 2,
                    "question": "send to background",
                    "answer": "bg"
                },
                {
                    "id": 4,
                    "question": "divide a file into several parts",
                    "answer": "cut"
                }
            ]
        },
        "userDto": {
            "id": 1,
            "name": "ania",
            "passwordHash": "$2a$10$BXILXZRu8YeAv6Z89ymBQObJ486skZ3P22apF.GAiI55pmXlO8Sk6",
            "role": "ROLE_CUSTOMER"
        }
    }

POST: localhost:8008/api/game
    {
        "date": "2021-06-13T13:45:21.827245",
        "points": 10,
        "gameMode": "flashcards",
        "ranking": true,
        "setOfFlashcards": {
            "id": 1,
            "category": "IT",
            "name": "linux commands",
            "flashcards": [
                {
                    "id": 1,
                    "question": "bourne-again shell",
                    "answer": "bash"
                },
                {
                    "id": 3,
                    "question": "concatenate and print",
                    "answer": "cat"
                },
                {
                    "id": 2,
                    "question": "send to background",
                    "answer": "bg"
                },
                {
                    "id": 4,
                    "question": "divide a file into several parts",
                    "answer": "cut"
                }
            ]
        },
        "userDto": {
            "id": 1,
            "name": "ania",
            "passwordHash": "$2a$10$BXILXZRu8YeAv6Z89ymBQObJ486skZ3P22apF.GAiI55pmXlO8Sk6",
            "role": "ROLE_CUSTOMER"
        }
    }
